<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Parallax Red Team Solutions</title>
    <link>https://parallax.red/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Parallax Red Team Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://parallax.red/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>https://parallax.red/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://parallax.red/about/</guid>
      <description>Hack the planet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coming Soon</title>
      <link>https://parallax.red/soon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://parallax.red/soon/</guid>
      <description>Coming soon! Until then, Hack the planet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>https://parallax.red/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://parallax.red/contact/</guid>
      <description>For more information on Parallax please reach out to our sales team: sales@parallax.red.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Offensive Security Services</title>
      <link>https://parallax.red/consulting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://parallax.red/consulting/</guid>
      <description>  Parallax Security provides a variety of bespoke offensive security solutions for your organization. Red Team Operations (Objective-based Testing) Application Security Assessments (Web, Native, Mobile) Penetration Testing (External, Internal) Reverse Engineering (Malware Analysis, Vulnerability Research) --  Let us know what you need to become more secure and we will help you.
Contact our Consulting Team</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parallax Cloak</title>
      <link>https://parallax.red/cloak/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://parallax.red/cloak/</guid>
      <description>Parallax Cloak simplifies deployment of resilient command and control infrastructure for red team operations.
With Cloak, you can quickly deploy traffic proxy servers to help hide critical infrastructure from the blue team, allowing you to stay online longer when servers are burned. No need to build redundant command and control servers, simply point and click your way to multiple redirectors, hops or reverse proxies. Parallax Cloak supports the following:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parallax Control</title>
      <link>https://parallax.red/control/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://parallax.red/control/</guid>
      <description>Parallax Control allows you to manage your command and control infrastructure through the Parallax dashboard. New pre-configured servers can be deployed, stopped and destroyed within minutes. No need to worry about compiling from source or trying to figure out why Terraform is failing. Need a new instance of Metasploit? Just point and click. A new SILENTTRINITY team server for your operation? Just point and click. Parallax Control supports the following command and control servers:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parallax Orc</title>
      <link>https://parallax.red/orc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://parallax.red/orc/</guid>
      <description>  Parallax Orc allows you to easily manage your red team operations all in one dashboard. With Orc, you can manage infrastructure, track operation findings and spending all and much more.
Contact our Sales Team</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
