<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Parallax Red Team Solutions</title>
    <link>https://parallax.red/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Parallax Red Team Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://parallax.red/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>https://parallax.red/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://parallax.red/about/</guid>
      <description>Hack the planet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coming Soon</title>
      <link>https://parallax.red/soon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://parallax.red/soon/</guid>
      <description>Coming soon! Until then, Hack the planet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>https://parallax.red/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://parallax.red/contact/</guid>
      <description>For more information on Parallax please reach out to our sales team: sales@parallax.red.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Offensive Security Services</title>
      <link>https://parallax.red/consulting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://parallax.red/consulting/</guid>
      <description>  Parallax Security provides a variety of bespoke offensive security solutions for your organization. Red Team Operations (Objective-based Testing) Application Security Assessments (Web, Native, Mobile) Penetration Testing (External, Internal) Reverse Engineering (Malware Analysis, Vulnerability Research) --  Let us know what you need to become more secure and we will help you.
Contact our Consulting Team</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parallax Cloak</title>
      <link>https://parallax.red/cloak/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://parallax.red/cloak/</guid>
      <description>Parallax Cloak simplifies deployment of resilient command and control infrastructure for red team operations.
With Cloak, you can instantly deploy traffic proxy servers to help hide critical infrastructure from the blue team, allowing you to stay online longer when servers are burned. You do not need to build redundant command and control servers anymore, simply point and click your way to multiple redirectors, hops or reverse proxies. Parallax Cloak supports the following:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parallax Control</title>
      <link>https://parallax.red/control/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://parallax.red/control/</guid>
      <description>Parallax Control allows you to manage your command and control infrastructure through the Parallax dashboard. New pre-configured servers can be deployed, stopped and destroyed quickly. No need to worry about compiling from source or trying to figure out why Terraform is failing. We&amp;rsquo;ve done the hard work for you. Command and control servers go up in seconds, and they are destroyed just as fast safely cleaning up your client&amp;rsquo;s sensitive data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parallax Orc</title>
      <link>https://parallax.red/orc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://parallax.red/orc/</guid>
      <description>  Parallax Orc allows you to easily manage your red team operations all in one dashboard. With Orc, you can manage infrastructure, track operation findings and spending all and much more.
Contact our Sales Team</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms and Conditions</title>
      <link>https://parallax.red/tos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://parallax.red/tos/</guid>
      <description>Last updated: May 06, 2021
Please read these terms and conditions carefully before using Our Service.Interpretation and Definitions Interpretation The words of which the initial letter is capitalized have meanings defined under the following conditions. The following definitions shall have the same meaning regardless of whether they appear in singular or in plural.
Definitions For the purposes of these Terms and Conditions:
  Affiliate means an entity that controls, is controlled by or is under common control with a party, where &amp;ldquo;control&amp;rdquo; means ownership of 50% or more of the shares, equity interest or other securities entitled to vote for election of directors or other managing authority.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
